<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>akregator.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAkregatorxx</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      Akregator is a news feed reader for the KDE desktop. It enables you to follow news sites, blogs and other RSS/Atom-enabled websites without the need to manually
      check for updates using a web browser. Akregator is designed to be both easy to use and to be powerful enough to read hundreds of news sources conveniently.
      It comes with Konqueror integration for adding news feeds and with an internal browser for easy news reading.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Akregator és un lector de fonts de notícies per a l'escriptori KDE. Permet que seguiu els llocs de notícies, blogs i altres llocs web amb el RSS/Atom habilitat, sense necessitat de comprovar manualment si hi ha actualitzacions mitjançant un navegador web. L'Akregator està dissenyat per a ser fàcil d'usar i prou potent com per llegir centenars de fonts de notícies convenientment. Ve amb integració amb el Konqueror per afegir els canals de notícies i amb un navegador intern per a facilitar la lectura de les notícies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Akregator is a news feed reader for the KDE desktop. It enables you to follow news sites, blogs and other RSS/Atom-enabled websites without the need to manually check for updates using a web browser. Akregator is designed to be both easy to use and to be powerful enough to read hundreds of news sources conveniently. It comes with Konqueror integration for adding news feeds and with an internal browser for easy news reading.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Akregator is en Mellenstroomwieser för den KDE-Schriefdisch. Du kannst dor de Ännern op Narichtensieden, Nettdaagböker un anner Sieden mit RSS-/Atom-Mellenströöm dor op mit nafolgen un bruukst dat nich vun Hand mit en Nettkieker maken. Akregator lett sik eenfach bruken, man Du kannst dor liekers hunnerte vun Narichtenborns mit eenfach lesen. Akregator warrt för't Tofögen vun nieg Mellenströöm na Konqueror inbunnen un hett en Nettkieker för't Lesen vun Narichten integreert.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Akregator is een lezer voor newsfeed voor het KDE bureaublad. Het laat u nieuwssites, blogs en andere RSS/Atom-ingeschakelde websites volgen zonder de noodzaak om handmatig te controleren op updates met een webbrowser. Akregator is ontworpen om zowel gemakkelijk te gebruiken als krachtig genoeg om honderden nieuwsbronnen gemakkelijk te volgen. Het komt met integratie met Konqueror voor toevoegen van nieuwsfeeds en met een interne browser voor gemakkelijke lezen van nieuws.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Akregator jest czytnikiem kanałów aktualności dla pulpitu KDE. Umożliwia śledzenie stron z aktualnościami, bloków i innych stron z włączonym  RSS/Atom bez potrzeby ręcznego sprawdzania uaktualnień poprzez przeglądarkę sieciową. Akregator został zaprojektowany, aby był zarówno łatwy w użyciu i na tyle zaawansowany, żeby mógł czytać z setek źródeł aktualności w sposób wygodny. Program jest zintegrowany z Konqueror, w celu dodawania kanałów aktualności. Dostarczany jest także z wewnętrzną przeglądarką dla łatwości czytania.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Akregator é um leitor de fontes de notícias para o ambiente de trabalho KDE. Permite-lhe seguir as páginas de notícias, 'blogs' e outras páginas com suporte para RSS/Atom sem a necessidade de pesquisar manualmente por actualizações com um navegador Web. O Akregator está desenhado para ser o mais simples de usar e poderoso o suficiente para ler centenas de fontes de notícias de forma conveniente. Vem com a integração com o Konqueror para adicionar fontes de notícias e com um navegador interno para a leitura simples de notícias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Akregator je čítačka noviniek pre prostredie KDE. Umožní vám sledovať servery noviniek, blogy a iné stránky s RSS/Atom bez potreby manuálnej kontroly noviniek pomocou webového prehliadača. Akregator je navrhnutý, aby bol jednoduchý na použitie a dostatočne silný na čítanie stoviek zdrojov noviniek. Obsahuje integráciu s Konquerorom pre pridanie noviniek a s interným prehliadačom na jednoduché čítanie noviniek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Akregator je bralnik novičarskih virov za namizje KDE. Omogoča sledenje stranem z novicami, blogom in drugim spletiščem, ki imajo vgrajeno podporo RSS/Atom, brez, da bi morali ročno preverjati za posodobitvami preko spletnega brskalnika. Akregator je zasnovan tako, da je hkrati enostaven za uporabo in dovolj zmogljiv za branje stotin novičarskih virov. Preko Konquerorja lahko dodajate novičarske vire, ima pa tudi notranji brskalnik za enostavno branje novic.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Akregator är en nyhetskanalläsare för KDE-skrivbordet. Den gör det möjligt att följa nyhetsplatser, bloggar och andra webbplatser som hanterar RSS/Atom utan att manuellt behöva leta efter uppdateringar med en webbläsare. Akregator är konstruerad för att både vara lätt att använda och kraftfull nog för att bekvämt läsa hundratals nyhetskällor. Integrering med Konqueror för att lägga till nyhetskanaler och en intern webbläsare för att enkelt kunna läsa nyheter ingår.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Akregator — програма для отримання подач новин для стільниці KDE. За її допомогою ви можете стежити за сайтами новин, блогами та іншими сайтами з даними RSS/Atom без потреби у перевірці вручну оновлень за допомогою програми для перегляду інтернету. Akregator розроблено простим у користуванні та достатньо потужним для зручного читання сотень джерел новин. У програмі передбачено інтеграцію із Konqueror  для додавання подач новин та вбудований переглядач для полегшення читання новин.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAkregator is a news feed reader for the KDE desktop. It enables you to follow news sites, blogs and other RSS/Atom-enabled websites without the need to manually check for updates using a web browser. Akregator is designed to be both easy to use and to be powerful enough to read hundreds of news sources conveniently. It comes with Konqueror integration for adding news feeds and with an internal browser for easy news reading.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://akregator.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=akregator</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdepim/akregator/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/akregator.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>akregator</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
