<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.akregator.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">أكريغاتور</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAkregatorxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Akregator</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      Akregator is a news feed reader for the KDE desktop. It enables you to follow news sites, blogs and other RSS/Atom-enabled websites without the need to manually
      check for updates using a web browser. Akregator is designed to be both easy to use and to be powerful enough to read hundreds of news sources conveniently.
      It comes with Konqueror integration for adding news feeds and with an internal browser for easy news reading.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">أكريغاتور قارئ تغذيات أخبار لسطح مكتب كدي. يمكّنك أكريغاتور من متابعة أخبار المواقع، والمدوّنات وأيّ مواقع وِبّ تمكّن RSS دون الحاجة لالتماس التّحديثات يدويًّا عبر متصفّح وِبّ. صُمِّم أكريغاتور ليكون سهل الاستخدام وقويًّا كفاية لقراءة مئات مصادر الأخبار براحة. كما يأتي مع تكامل كنكر لإضافة تغذيات الأخبار ومتصفّح داخليّ لتسهيل قراءة الأخبار.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Akregator és un lector de fonts de notícies per a l'escriptori KDE. Permet que seguiu els llocs de notícies, blogs i altres llocs web amb el RSS/Atom habilitat, sense necessitat de comprovar manualment si hi ha actualitzacions mitjançant un navegador web. L'Akregator està dissenyat per a ser fàcil d'usar i prou potent per a llegir centenars de fonts de notícies convenientment. Ve amb integració amb el Konqueror per afegir els canals de notícies i amb un navegador intern per a facilitar la lectura de les notícies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'Akregator és un lector de fonts de notícies per a l'escriptori KDE. Permet que seguiu els llocs de notícies, blogs i altres llocs web amb el RSS/Atom habilitat, sense necessitat de comprovar manualment si hi ha actualitzacions mitjançant un navegador web. L'Akregator està dissenyat per a ser fàcil d'usar i prou potent per a llegir centenars de fonts de notícies convenientment. Ve amb integració amb el Konqueror per afegir els canals de notícies i amb un navegador intern per a facilitar la lectura de les notícies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Akregator is a news feed reader for the KDE desktop. It enables you to follow news sites, blogs and other RSS/Atom-enabled websites without the need to manually check for updates using a web browser. Akregator is designed to be both easy to use and to be powerful enough to read hundreds of news sources conveniently. It comes with Konqueror integration for adding news feeds and with an internal browser for easy news reading.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Akregator es un lector de noticias para el escritorio KDE. Le permite seguir sitios de noticias, blogs y otros sitios web con RSS/Atom activado, sin la necesidad de comprobar actualizaciones manualmente con un navegador web. Akregator está diseñado para ser fácil de usar y ser lo bastante potente para leer cientos de fuentes de noticias. Viene con integración con Konqueror para añadir fuentes de noticias y un navegador interno para la lectura fácil de las noticias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Akregator on uutissyötteenlukija KDE-työpöydälle. Sen avulla voit seurata uutissivustoja, blogeja ja muita RSS/Atom-sivustoja tarvitsematta käydä sivulla verkkoselaimella. Akregator on suunniteltu sekä helpoksi käyttää että riittävän tehokkaaksi seurata satoja uutislähteitä yhtä aikaa. Siinä on myös Konqueror-integrointi uutissyötteiden lisäämiseksi ja sisäinen selain uutisten lukemiseksi helpommin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Akregator est un lecteur de flux RSS pour le bureau KDE. Il vous permet de suivre des sites d'information, des blogs ou tout autre site web prenant en charge les flux RSS ou Atom, sans avoir besoin d'ouvrir les pages dans votre navigateur. Akregator est conçu pour être à la fois facile à utiliser et suffisamment puissant pour manipuler simplement des centaines de sources. Il peut s'intégrer à Konqueror pour y ajouter la gestion des flux, et il fournit un navigateur interne pour lire facilement les articles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Akregator é un lector de fontes de novas para o escritorio de KDE. Permítelle facer un seguimento de sitios de novas, blogues e outros sitios web que fornezan fontes de novas RSS ou Atom, sen a necesitade de comprobar manualmente se hai novidades usando un navegador web. Akregator está deseñado para ser tanto fácil de usar como potente dabondo para ler centros de fontes de novas de maneira cómoda. Inclúe integración en Konqueror para engadir fontes de novas e un navegador web integrado para ler novas facilmente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az Akregator egy hírolvasó alkalmazás a KDE-hez. Lehetővé teszi híroldalak, blogok, és más RSS/Atom források követését anélkül, hogy kézzel kellene ellenőriznie a frissítéseket webböngészőjében. Úgy tervezték, hogy egyszerű legyen használni, ugyanakkor hatékonyan és kényelmesen lehessen követni akár több száz hírforrást is. A Konqueror integrációval egyszerűen adhat hozzá új forrásokat, a beépített böngésző pedig megkönnyíti a hírek olvasását.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Akregator è un lettore di fonti di notizie per il desktop di KDE. Ti permette di seguire siti di notizie, blog e altri siti che dispongono di fonti RSS/Atom senza la necessità di controllare manualmente gli aggiornamenti con un browser web. Akregator è progettato per essere allo stesso tempo semplice usare e in grado di poter leggere comodamente centinaia di fonti di notizie. È provvisto di integrazione con Konqueror per l'aggiunta di fonti di notizie e con un browser interno per una facile consultazione delle notizie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Akregator는 KDE 뉴스 피드 리더입니다. 뉴스 사이트, 블로그, RSS/Atom 지원 웹 사이트에 웹 브라우저로 직접 방문하지 않고 업데이트를 따라갈 수 있습니다. Akregator는 다량의 뉴스 사이트를 편하게 읽을 수 있음과 동시에 쉽게 사용할 수 있도록 설계되었습니다. Konqueror에서 직접 뉴스 피드를 추가할 수 있으며 쉬운 글 읽기를 위한 내장 웹 브라우저가 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Akregator er en nyhetsleser for KDE-skrivebordet. Med Akregator kan du følge nyhets-nettsteder, blogger og andre nettsteder som bruker RSS/Atom uten å ses etter manuelt med en nettleser. Akregator er designet til å være både lett å bruke og kraftig nok til å kunne lese hundrevis av nyhetskilder. Det har integrering med Konqueror for å legge til nyhetskilder og en intern nettleser for lett tilgang til nyheter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Akregator is en Mellenstroomwieser för den KDE-Schriefdisch. Du kannst dor de Ännern op Narichtensieden, Nettdaagböker un anner Sieden mit RSS-/Atom-Mellenströöm dor op mit nafolgen un bruukst dat nich vun Hand mit en Nettkieker maken. Akregator lett sik eenfach bruken, man Du kannst dor liekers hunnerte vun Narichtenborns mit eenfach lesen. Akregator warrt för't Tofögen vun nieg Mellenströöm na Konqueror inbunnen un hett en Nettkieker för't Lesen vun Narichten integreert.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Akregator is een lezer voor newsfeed voor het KDE bureaublad. Het laat u nieuwssites, blogs en andere RSS/Atom-ingeschakelde websites volgen zonder de noodzaak om handmatig te controleren op updates met een webbrowser. Akregator is ontworpen om zowel gemakkelijk te gebruiken als krachtig genoeg om honderden nieuwsbronnen gemakkelijk te volgen. Het komt met integratie met Konqueror voor toevoegen van nieuwsfeeds en met een interne browser voor gemakkelijke lezen van nieuws.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Akregator jest czytnikiem kanałów aktualności dla pulpitu KDE. Umożliwia śledzenie stron z aktualnościami, bloków i innych stron z włączonym  RSS/Atom bez potrzeby ręcznego sprawdzania uaktualnień poprzez przeglądarkę sieciową. Akregator został zaprojektowany, aby był zarówno łatwy w użyciu i na tyle zaawansowany, żeby mógł czytać z setek źródeł aktualności w sposób wygodny. Program jest zintegrowany z Konqueror, w celu dodawania kanałów aktualności. Dostarczany jest także z wewnętrzną przeglądarką dla łatwości czytania.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Akregator é um leitor de fontes de notícias para o ambiente de trabalho KDE. Permite-lhe seguir as páginas de notícias, 'blogs' e outras páginas com suporte para RSS/Atom sem a necessidade de pesquisar manualmente por actualizações com um navegador Web. O Akregator está desenhado para ser o mais simples de usar e poderoso o suficiente para ler centenas de fontes de notícias de forma conveniente. Vem com a integração com o Konqueror para adicionar fontes de notícias e com um navegador interno para a leitura simples de notícias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Akregator é um leitor de fontes de notícias para o KDE. Permite-lhe acompanhar as páginas de notícias, blogs e outras páginas com suporte a RSS/Atom, sem a necessidade usar um navegador Web para verificar se existem atualizações. O Akregator foi projetado para ser simples de usar e, ao mesmo tempo, poderoso o suficiente para ler centenas de fontes de notícias de forma conveniente. Ele possui integração com o Konqueror para adicionar fontes de notícias e um navegador interno para leitura de notícias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Akregator — программа для чтения лент новостей от KDE. Она позволяет вам следить за новыми публикациями на сайтах без необходимости периодически заходить на них. Akregator прост в использовании, но в то же время рассчитан на удобное отслеживание сотен источников новостей. Читать новости из лент можно прямо в окне Akregator. Для веб-браузера Konqueror есть модуль для добавления новых лент в Akregator, этот модуль входит в пакет konq-plugins.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Akregator je čítačka noviniek pre prostredie KDE. Umožní vám sledovať servery noviniek, blogy a iné stránky s RSS/Atom bez potreby manuálnej kontroly noviniek pomocou webového prehliadača. Akregator je navrhnutý, aby bol jednoduchý na použitie a dostatočne silný na čítanie stoviek zdrojov noviniek. Obsahuje integráciu s Konquerorom pre pridanie noviniek a s interným prehliadačom na jednoduché čítanie noviniek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Akregator je bralnik novičarskih virov za namizje KDE. Omogoča sledenje stranem z novicami, blogom in drugim spletiščem, ki imajo vgrajeno podporo RSS/Atom, brez, da bi morali ročno preverjati za posodobitvami preko spletnega brskalnika. Akregator je zasnovan tako, da je hkrati enostaven za uporabo in dovolj zmogljiv za branje stotin novičarskih virov. Preko Konquerorja lahko dodajate novičarske vire, ima pa tudi notranji brskalnik za enostavno branje novic.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Akregator är en nyhetskanalläsare för KDE-skrivbordet. Den gör det möjligt att följa nyhetsplatser, bloggar och andra webbplatser som hanterar RSS/Atom utan att manuellt behöva leta efter uppdateringar med en webbläsare. Akregator är konstruerad för att både vara lätt att använda och kraftfull nog för att bekvämt läsa hundratals nyhetskällor. Integrering med Konqueror för att lägga till nyhetskanaler och en intern webbläsare för att enkelt kunna läsa nyheter ingår.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Akregator KDE masa üstü için haber beslemeleri okuyucusudur. Haber sitelerini, blogları ve diğer RSS/Atom-etkin web sitelerini web tarayıcı ile elle güncellemeler için kontrol etmenize gerek kalmadan takip etmenize olanak sağlar. Akregator hem kullanımı kolay hem yüzlerce haber kaynağını kolay şekilde okuyabileceğiniz kadar güçlü olması için tasarlanmıştır. Haber kaynaklarını eklemek için Konqueror tümleştirmesi ile ve kolay haber okuma için dahili bir tarayıcı ile gelir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Akregator — програма для отримання подач новин для стільниці KDE. За її допомогою ви можете стежити за сайтами новин, блогами та іншими сайтами з даними RSS/Atom без потреби у перевірці вручну оновлень за допомогою програми для перегляду інтернету. Akregator розроблено простим у користуванні та достатньо потужним для зручного читання сотень джерел новин. У програмі передбачено інтеграцію із Konqueror  для додавання подач новин та вбудований переглядач для полегшення читання новин.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAkregator is a news feed reader for the KDE desktop. It enables you to follow news sites, blogs and other RSS/Atom-enabled websites without the need to manually check for updates using a web browser. Akregator is designed to be both easy to use and to be powerful enough to read hundreds of news sources conveniently. It comes with Konqueror integration for adding news feeds and with an internal browser for easy news reading.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Akregator 是 KDE 桌面系統的新聞 feed 閱讀器。它讓您可以輕鬆取得新聞站台、部落格與其它 RSS/Atom 文章來源，不需要自己親自去每個站台看看有沒有新聞章。Akregator 設計成非常易用，並且夠強大，方便讀取上百個新聞來源。它也可以跟 Konqueror 整合，使用內部瀏覽器方便閱讀新聞。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://akregator.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=akregator</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdepim/akregator/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/akregator.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>akregator</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
