<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.akregator.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">أكريغاتور</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="az">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Акрегатор</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Акрегатор</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Akregatör</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAkregatorxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Akregator</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Akregator</name>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name>The KDE Community</name>
    <url>https://kde.org</url>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>
      Akregator is a news feed reader. It enables you to follow news sites, blogs and other RSS/Atom-enabled websites without the need to manually
      check for updates using a web browser. Akregator is designed to be both easy to use and to be powerful enough to read hundreds of news sources conveniently.
      It comes with a fast search, advanced archiving functionality and an internal browser for easy news reading.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">«أكريغاتور» هو قارئ تغذيات الأخبار. يتيح لك «أكريغاتور» متابعة أخبار المواقع، والمدوّنات وأيّ مواقع أخرى تدعم RSS/Atom، ذلك لإلغاء حاجة التماس التّحديثات يدويًّا عبر متصفّح الوبّ. صُمِّم «أكريغاتور» ليكون سهل الاستخدام وقويًّا كفاية لقراءة مئات مصادر الأخبار براحة. كما يأتي مع تكامل «كنكر» لإضافة تغذيات الأخبار وأيضًا يحتوي متصفّحًا داخليًّا لتسهيل قراءة الأخبار.</p>
    <p xml:lang="az">Akregator xəbər lenti oxuma tətbiqidir. Yeni xəbərləri izləmək üçün veb bələdçiyə ehtiyac olmadan xəbər saytlarını, blogları və digər RSS/Atom funksiyası olan veb saytlarını izləməyə imkan verir. Akregator həm istifadəsi asan, həm də yüzlərlə xəbər mənbələrini rahatlıqla oxuyacaq qədər güclü hazırlanmışdır. Sürətli axtarış, təkmilləşdirilmış arxivləşdirmə funksiyası və asan xəbər oxumaq üçün daxili veb bələdçi ilə təchiz olunmuşdur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Akregator е програма за преглед на емисии. Тя ви позволява да следвате сайтове за новини, блогове и други уебсайтове, поддържащи RSS/Atom, без да е необходимо да проверявате ръчно за актуализации, използвайки уеб браузър. Akregator е проектиран да бъде едновременно лесен за използване и да бъде достатъчно мощен, за да прочете удобно стотици източници на новини. Той идва с бързо търсене, усъвършенствана функционалност на архивирането и вътрешен браузър за лесно четене на новини.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Akregator és un lector de fonts de notícies. Permet que seguiu els llocs de notícies, blogs i altres llocs web amb el RSS/Atom habilitat, sense necessitat de comprovar manualment si hi ha actualitzacions mitjançant un navegador web. L'Akregator està dissenyat per a ser fàcil d'usar i prou potent per a llegir centenars de fonts de notícies convenientment. Ve amb característiques de cerca ràpida, arxivat avançat i amb un navegador intern per a facilitar la lectura de les notícies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Akregator és un lector de fonts de notícies. Permet que seguiu els llocs de notícies, blogs i altres llocs web amb el RSS/Atom habilitat, sense necessitat de comprovar manualment si hi ha actualitzacions mitjançant un navegador web. Akregator està dissenyat per a ser fàcil d'utilitzar i prou potent per a llegir centenars de fonts de notícies convenientment. Ve amb característiques de busca ràpida, arxivat avançat i amb un navegador intern per a facilitar la lectura de les notícies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Akregator je čtečka kanálů novinek. Umožňuje vám sledovat nové stránky, blogy a jiné stránky se zapnutou podporou RSS/Atom bez potřeby osobní návštěvy webu pomocí prohlížeče. Akregator je navržen tak, aby byl snadno použitelný a dostatečně výkonný aby mohl pohodlně číst ze stovek zdrojů novinek. Obsahuje rychlý vyhledávač, pokročilé funkce archivování a interní prohlížeč pro snadné čtení novinek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Akregator er en nyhedsfeed-læser. Den lader dig følge nyhedssider, blogs og andre websider udstyret med RSS/Atom uden det er nødvendigt manuelt at tjekke for opdateringer i en webbrowser. Akregator er designet til både at være nem at bruge og at være kraftfuld nok til at læse hundredvis af nyhedskilder på bekvem vis. Den kommer med hurtig søgning, avanceret arkiveringsfunktionalitet og en indbygget browser til nem nyhedslæsning.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Akregator ist ein Nachrichtensammler. Sie können damit Nachrichtenseiten, Blogs und andere Webseiten mit RSS/Atom-Quellen abonnieren, ohne die Seite manuell mit dem Webbrowser zu besuchen. Akregator ist einfach zu bedienen und zugleich leistungsfähig genug, um bequem hunderte Nachrichtenquellen zu lesen. Akregator enthält eine schnelle Suche, erweiterte Archivierungsfunktionen und zum einfachen Lesen ist ein Webbrowser integriert.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Akregator είναι ένας συναθροιστής ροών περιεχομένου. Σας επιτρέπει να ακολουθείτε ιστοτόπους, ιστολόγια και άλλους ιστοχώρους με ενεργό το RSS/Atom χωρίς να χρειάζεται να αναζητάτε την ενημέρωση με τον περιηγητή ιστού. Το Akregator σχεδιάστηκε για ευκολία στη χρήση αλλά και να είναι αρκετά ισχυρό για την απρόσκοπτη ανάγνωση εκατοντάδων ειδήσεων από διάφορες πηγές. Περιλαμβάνει ταχεία αναζήτηση, προηγμένη λειτουργία αρχειοθέτησης και έναν εσωτερικό περιηγητή για εύκολη ανάγνωση.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Akregator is a news feed reader. It enables you to follow news sites, blogs and other RSS/Atom-enabled websites without the need to manually check for updates using a web browser. Akregator is designed to be both easy to use and to be powerful enough to read hundreds of news sources conveniently. It comes with a fast search, advanced archiving functionality and an internal browser for easy news reading.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Akregator estas novaĵflua legilo. Ĝi ebligas vin sekvi novaĵejojn, blogojn kaj aliajn RSS/Atom-kapablajn retejojn sen devi permane kontroli pri ĝisdatigoj uzante retumilon. Akregator estas dezajnata por esti ambaŭ facile uzebla kaj sufiĉe potenca to legi centojn da novaĵfontoj konvene. Ĝi venas kun interna foliumilo por facila legado de novaĵoj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Akregator es un lector de fuentes noticias. Le permite seguir sitios de noticias, blogs y otros sitios web con RSS/Atom activado, sin la necesidad de comprobar actualizaciones manualmente con un navegador web. Akregator está diseñado, tanto para ser fácil de usar, como ser lo bastante potente para leer cientos de fuentes de noticias adecuadamente. Viene con búsqueda rápida, funcionalidad avanzada de archivado y un navegador interno para la lectura fácil de las noticias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Akregator on uudistevoogude lugeja. See võimaldab jälgida uudistesaite, ajaveebe ja muid RSS/Atomi võimekusega veebilehti, ilma et peaksid pidevalt nende uuendusi veebibrauseris kontrollima. Akregator on mõeldud korraga nii hõlpsasti kasutatavaks kui ka piisavalt võimsaks, et lugeda korraga mugavalt sadu uudisteallikaid. Akregator pakub kiire otsingu võimalust, põhjalikke arhiveerimise valikuid ning isemist brauserit uudiste lihtsamaks lugemiseks.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Akregator, albiste-jarioak irakurtzeko aplikazio bat da. Albiste-guneetako, blogetako eta RSS/Atom gaituta duten beste webguneetako berriak irakurtzeko aukera eskaintzen dizu, web arakatzaile bat erabiliz eguneratzeen berri, eskuz,egiaztatzen ibili beharrik izan gabe. Akregator, erabilerraza izateko eta ehunaka albiste sorburutatik egokiro irakurtzeko diseinatuta dago. Bilaketa azkarra, artxibatzeko funtzionaltasun aurreratua eta albisteak erraz irakurtzeko barneko arakatzaile batekin dator.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Akregator on uutissyötelukija, jonka avulla voit seurata uutissivustoja, blogeja ja muita RSS/Atom-sivustoja käymättä sivuilla selaimella. Akregator on suunniteltu sekä helppokäyttöiseksi että riittävän tehokkaaksi satojen uutislähteiden seuraamiseksi samanaikaisesti. Siinä on nopea haku, kehittynyt arkistointitoiminto ja sisäinen selain uutisten lukemiseksi juohevasti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Akregator est un lecteur de flux. Il vous permet de suivre des sites d'informations, des blogs ou tout autre site Internet prenant en charge les flux « RSS » ou « Atom », sans avoir besoin de vérifier manuellement les pages dans votre navigateur. Akregator est conçu pour être à la fois facile à utiliser et suffisamment puissant pour accéder simplement à des centaines de sources. Il intègre une recherche rapide, des fonctionnalités d'archivage avancées et un navigateur interne pour lire facilement les articles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Akregator é un lector de fontes de novas. Permítelle facer un seguimento de sitios de novas, bitácoras e outros sitios web que fornezan fontes de novas RSS ou Atom, sen a necesitade de comprobar manualmente se hai actualizacións usando un navegador web. Akregator está deseñado para ser tanto fácil de usar como potente dabondo para ler centos de fontes de novas de maneira cómoda. Inclúe unha busca rápida, funcionalidade avanzada de arquivo e un navegador web integrado para ler novas facilmente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Akregator הוא מציג ערוצי חדשות. הוא מאפשר לך לעקוב אחר ערוצי חדשות, בלוגים ומגוון אתרים נוספים שתומכים ב־RSS/Atom ללא צורך בחיפוש ידני של עדכונים עם דפדפן. Akregator תוכן להיות קל לשימוש ועתיר בתכונות לפחות עד לרמה שאפשר לקרוא באמצעותו ממאות מקורות של חדשות בצורה נוחה. החיפוש שלו מהיר, יש לו יכולות ארכיון מתקדמות ודפדפן פנימי לקריאת חדשות בקלות.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az Akregator egy hírolvasó alkalmazás. Lehetővé teszi híroldalak, blogok, és más RSS/Atom források követését anélkül, hogy kézzel kellene ellenőriznie a frissítéseket webböngészőjében. Úgy tervezték, hogy egyszerű legyen használni, ugyanakkor hatékonyan és kényelmesen lehessen követni akár több száz hírforrást is. A keresője gyors, az archiválási funkciói fejlettek, a beépített böngésző pedig megkönnyíti a hírek olvasását.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Akregator es un lector de syndication. Illo te habilita per sequer sitos de novas, blogs e altere sitos web activate per RSS/Atom sin le necessitate de verificar manualmente actualisationes usante cerca web. Akregator es designate per esser sia manual de usar e per esser assatis potente per leger centos de nove fontes convenientemente. Illo ha cerca rapide, functionalitate de archivar avantiate e un explorator interne per un facile lectura de novas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Akregator adalah pembaca feed berita. Ini memungkinkan Anda untuk mengikuti situs berita, blog, dan situs RSS/Atom-yang-difungsikan lainnya tanpa harus memeriksa secara manual pembaruan berita menggunakan penelusur web. Akregator telah didesain menjadi mudah digunakan dan menjadi cukup hebat untuk membaca ratusan sumber berita secara nyaman. Ini hadir dengan pencarian yang cepat fungsionalitas pengarsipan terkemuka dan memiliki sebuah penelusur internal untuk kemudahan membaca berita.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Akregator er fréttalesaraforrit. Með því geturðu fylgst með fréttasíðum, bloggum og öðrum vefsíðum sem bjóða upp á RSS/Atom-strauma, án þess að þurfa að fletta þeim sífellt upp í vafra. Akregator er bæði auðvelt í notkun og nógu öflugt til að geta fylgst með hundruðum af fréttauppsprettum með léttum leik. Forritið er með hraðvirka leit, ítarlega safnvistunareiginleika og innbyggðan vafra til að auðvelda fréttalestur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Akregator è un lettore di fonti di notizie. Ti permette di seguire siti di notizie, blog e altri siti che dispongono di fonti RSS/Atom senza la necessità di controllare manualmente gli aggiornamenti con un browser web. Akregator è progettato per essere allo stesso tempo semplice usare e in grado di poter leggere comodamente centinaia di fonti di notizie. È provvisto di ricerca rapida, di funzioni avanzate di archiviazione e di un browser interno per una facile consultazione delle notizie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Akregator სიახლეების წასაკითხი პროგრამაა. ის საშუალებას გაძლევთ, მიჰყვეთ სიახლეების საიტებს, ბლოგებს და სხვა RSS/Atom-ჩართულ ვებგვერდებს განახლებების ხელით შემოწმების საჭიროების გარეშე. Akregator-ი ორივე, ადვილი და მძლავრია, რომ ასობით სიახლის წყარო ადეკვატურად დაამუშაოს. მას ასევე მოჰყვება სწრაფი ძებნა, განვითარებული არქივირების ფუნქციონალი და სიახლეების ადვილად წასაკითხად, შიდა ბრაუზერი.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Akregator는 뉴스 피드 리더입니다. 뉴스 사이트, 블로그, RSS/Atom 지원 웹사이트에 웹 브라우저로 직접 방문하지 않고 업데이트를 따라갈 수 있습니다. Akregator는 다량의 뉴스 사이트를 편하게 읽을 수 있음과 동시에 쉽게 사용할 수 있도록 설계되었습니다. 빠른 검색, 글 보관 기능을 지원하며 쉽게 글을 읽을 수 있는 내장 웹 브라우저가 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Akregator yra naujienų sklaidos kanalų skaitytuvė. Ji leidžia sekti naujienų internetines svetaines, tinklaraščius bei kitas RSS/Atom įgalintas internetines svetaines be būtinybės rankiniu būdu tikrinti svetainės atnaujinimus naudojant saityno naršyklę. Akregator sukurta, kad ja būtų lengva naudotis ir, kad ji būtų pakankamai galinga siekiant patogiai skaityti šimtus naujienų iš įvairių šaltinių. Akregator patogiam naujienų skaitymui pateikiama su greita paieška, išplėstiniu archyvavimo funkcionalumu ir vidine naršykle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Akregator“ ir ziņu plūsmu lasītājs. Šī programma ļauj sekot ziņu lapām, emuāriem un citām vietnēm, kurās darbojas „RSS/Atom“ funkcija, ļaujot izvairīties no manuālas ziņu pārbaudes tīmekļa pārlūkprogrammā. „Akregator“ ir veidots, lai būtu viegli lietojams, bet arī pietiekami jaudīgs ērtai simtiem ziņu avotu pārlūkošanai. Tam ir iebūvēta ātra meklēšana, paplašināta arhivēšanas funkcionalitāte un iekšējs pārlūks vieglai ziņu lasīšanai.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Akregator is een lezer voor newsfeed. Het laat u nieuwssites, blogs en andere RSS/Atom-ingeschakelde websites volgen zonder de noodzaak om handmatig te controleren op updates met een webbrowser. Akregator is ontworpen om zowel gemakkelijk te gebruiken als krachtig genoeg om honderden nieuwsbronnen gemakkelijk te volgen. Het komt met een snel zoeken, geavanceerd archiveren en met een interne browser voor gemakkelijk lezen van nieuws.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Akregator er ein nyheitskjeldelesar. Han kan følgja nyheitsstadar, bloggar og andre nettstadar som tilbyr RSS/Atom-kjelder utan at du treng følgja med på oppdateringar manuelt. Akregator er utforma for å vera lett å bruka og kraftig nok til å visa hundrevis av nyheitskjelder på ein tilgjengeleg måte. Han kjem med eit snøggsøk, funksjonar for avansert arkivering og ein innebygd nettlesar for vising av nyheiter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Akregator jest czytnikiem kanałów aktualności. Umożliwia śledzenie stron z aktualnościami, bloków i innych stron z włączonym  RSS/Atom bez potrzeby ręcznego sprawdzania uaktualnień poprzez przeglądarkę sieciową. Akregator został zaprojektowany, aby był zarówno łatwy w użyciu i na tyle zaawansowany, żeby mógł czytać z setek źródeł aktualności w sposób wygodny. Program umożliwia szybkie wyszukiwanie, rozbudowane archiwizowanie oraz wewnętrzną przeglądarkę dla łatwości odczytywania wieści.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Akregator é um leitor de fontes de notícias. Permite-lhe seguir as páginas de notícias, 'blogs' e outras páginas com suporte para RSS/Atom sem a necessidade de pesquisar manualmente por actualizações com um navegador Web. O Akregator está desenhado para ser o mais simples de usar e poderoso o suficiente para ler centenas de fontes de notícias de forma conveniente. Vem com a integração com o Konqueror para adicionar fontes de notícias e com um navegador interno para a leitura simples de notícias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Akregator é um leitor de fontes de notícias. Permite-lhe acompanhar as páginas de notícias, blogs e outras páginas com suporte a RSS/Atom, sem a necessidade usar um navegador Web para verificar se existem atualizações. O Akregator foi projetado para ser simples de usar e, ao mesmo tempo, poderoso o suficiente para ler centenas de fontes de notícias de forma conveniente. Ele possui uma pesquisa rápida, funcionalidade de arquivamento avançada e um navegador interno para leitura de notícias.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Akregator — программа для чтения лент новостей. Она позволяет вам следить за новыми публикациями на сайтах без необходимости периодически заходить на них. Akregator прост в использовании, но в то же время рассчитан на удобное отслеживание сотен источников новостей. Читать новости из лент можно прямо в окне Akregator. Приложение обладает функцией быстрого поиска, поддерживает работу с архивами новостей и содержит встроенный браузер для чтения.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Akregator je program na čítanie správ. Umožňuje vám sledovať spravodajské weby, blogy a iné webové stránky s podporou RSS/Atom bez potreby ručnej kontroly aktualizácií pomocou webového prehliadača. Akregator je navrhnutý tak, aby sa dal ľahko používať a aby bol dostatočne výkonný na pohodlné čítanie stoviek spravodajských zdrojov. Je dodávaný s rýchlym vyhľadávaním, pokročilými funkciami archivácie a interným prehliadačom pre ľahké čítanie správ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Akregator je bralnik novic. Omogoča vam spremljanje novic, spletnih mest, blogovin drugih spletnih mest, ki podpirajo RSS/Atom, ne da bi bilo treba ročno preverjatiposodobitve s pomočjo spletnega brskalnika. Akregator je zasnovan tako, da je enostaven za uporaboin da bo dovolj močan, da lahko priročno bere na stotine virov novic. Omogoča s hitro iskanje, napredne funkcije arhiviranja in internibrskalnik za enostavno branje novic.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Akregator är en nyhetskanalläsare. Den gör det möjligt att följa nyhetsplatser, bloggar och andra webbplatser som hanterar RSS/Atom utan att manuellt behöva leta efter uppdateringar med en webbläsare. Akregator är konstruerad för att både vara lätt att använda och kraftfull nog för att bekvämt läsa hundratals nyhetskällor. Den levereras med snabb sökning, avancerad arkiveringsfunktionalitet och en intern webbläsare för att enkelt kunna läsa nyheter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Akregatör, bir haber beslemesi okuyucusudur. Haber sitelerini, blogları ve diğer RSS/Atom beslemelerinin etkin olduğu web sitelerini web tarayıcısı ile elle güncellemeler için denetlemenize gerek kalmadan takip etmenize olanak sağlar. Akregatör hem kullanımı kolay hem yüzlerce haber kaynağını kolay şekilde okuyabileceğiniz kadar güçlü olması için tasarlanmıştır. Haber kaynaklarını eklemek için Konqueror tümleştirmesi ile ve kolay haber okuma için dahili bir tarayıcı ile gelir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Akregator — програма для отримання подач новин. За її допомогою ви можете стежити за сайтами новин, блогами та іншими сайтами з даними RSS/Atom без потреби у перевірці вручну оновлень за допомогою програми для перегляду інтернету. Akregator розроблено простим у користуванні та достатньо потужним для зручного читання сотень джерел новин. У програмі передбачено швидкий пошук, розширені можливості із архівування та вбудований переглядач для полегшення читання новин.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAkregator is a news feed reader. It enables you to follow news sites, blogs and other RSS/Atom-enabled websites without the need to manually check for updates using a web browser. Akregator is designed to be both easy to use and to be powerful enough to read hundreds of news sources conveniently. It comes with a fast search, advanced archiving functionality and an internal browser for easy news reading.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Akregator 是新闻源阅读器。 它使您能够关注新闻网站、博客和其他启用 RSS/Atom 的网站，而无需使用网络浏览器手动检查更新。 Akregator 的设计既易于使用，又足够强大以方便地阅读数以百计的新闻源。 它带有快速搜索、强大的存档功能和内部浏览器以方便阅读新闻。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Akregator 一款新聞 feed 閱讀器。它讓您可以輕鬆取得新聞站台、部落格與其它 RSS/Atom 文章來源，不需要自己親自去每個站台看看有沒有新文章。Akregator 設計成非常易用，並且夠強大，方便讀取上百個新聞來源。它也有快速搜尋與進階封存功能，以及內部瀏覽器以供簡易閱讀新聞。</p>
  </description>
  <summary>Keep up with your feeds</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">واكب تغذياتك</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Следете емисиите си</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Mantenir-se al dia amb les vostres fonts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mantindre's al dia amb les vostres fonts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Aktualiĝu pri viaj abonfluoj</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Manténgase al día con sus fuentes de noticias</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Jarioekin egunean egon zaitezen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Suivez vos flux</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">להתעדכן במה שמעניין אותך</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Tartson lépést a hírekkel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Mantene le passo con tu syndicationes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Resta aggiornato con le tue fonti</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ადევნეთ თვალყური თქვენს ლენტებს</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Uw feeds bijhouden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Nie przegap niczego, co się dzieje na twoich kanałach</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Acompanhe seus feeds</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Bodite na tekočem s svojimi viri</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Beslemelerinizi takip edin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Стежте за вашими стрічками новин</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKeep up with your feedsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">跟上您的 feed 的更新</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://kontact.kde.org/components/akregator/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=akregator</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=akregator</url>
  <url type="donation">https://kde.org/community/donations/?app=akregator&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://invent.kde.org/pim/akregator/</url>
  <url type="contact">https://go.kde.org/matrix/#/#kontact:kde.org</url>
  <url type="contribute">https://community.kde.org/Get_Involved/</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.akgregator.desktop</launchable>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>Qt</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Reading feeds in Kontact with Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">يقرأ التغذيات في كونتك بواسطة أكريغاتور</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="az">Xəbərlərin Kontact-da Akregator ilə oxunması</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Преглед на емисии в Kontact с Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Llegint fonts al Kontact amb l'Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Llegint fonts en Kontact amb Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Čtení kanálů v Kontactu pomocí Akregatoru</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Læser feeds i Kontact med Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Nachrichtenquellen in Kontact mit Akregator lesen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Ανάγνωση ροών στο Kontact με το Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Reading feeds in Kontact with Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Legi fluojn en Kontact per Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Leyendo fuentes en Kontact con Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Uudistevoogude lugemine Kontactis Akregatori vahendusel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Jarioak Kontact-en Akregator erabiliz irakurtzea</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Syötteiden lukeminen Kontactissa Akregatorilla</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Lire des flux dans Kontact avec Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Lendo fontes en Kontact con Akregator.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">קריאת ערוצי עדכונים ב־Kontact עם Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Hírek olvasása Akregatorral Kontactban</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Leger syndicationes in Kontact con Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Membaca feed di Kontact menggunakan Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Lestur strauma í Kontact með Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Lettura di notizie in Kontact con Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">წაიკთხეთ სიახლეები Kontact-ში Akragator-თან ერთად</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Akregator로 Kontact에서 피드 읽기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Sklaidos kanalų skaitymas Kontact programoje naudojant Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Plūsmu lasīšana „Kontact“ programmā ar „Akregator“</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Feeds lezen in Kontact met Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Lesing av kjelder i Kontact ved hjelp av Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Czytanie kanałów w Kontact przy użyciu Akregatora</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Leitura de fontes no Kontact com o Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Leitura de fontes de notícias no Kontact com o Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Чтение лент новостей в Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Čítanie informačných kanálov v Kontact s Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Branje virov v Kontaktu z Akregatorjem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Läsa kanaler i Kontact med Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Akregatör ile Kontak’ta beslemeleri okuma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Читання подач у Kontact за допомогою Akregator</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxReading feeds in Kontact with Akregatorxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">用 Akregator 在 Kontact 读取订阅源</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">使用 Akregator 在 Kontact 閱讀 Feed</caption>
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/akregator/akregator.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>akregator</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="6.0.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="6.0.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="6.0.0" date="2024-02-28">
      <url>https://kde.org/announcements/megarelease/6/</url>
      <description>
        <p>This release port Akgregator to Qt6 and tweak a bit the design of the app.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.24.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#fbd7c9</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#7e2b21</color>
  </branding>
</component>
